The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight.
And despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world
and to become the next Wizard King.
Awesome.
This will also be so beautiful,
and born in 何も火
I'll see you next time.
未来は自分で切り開くんだって
止めとなく溢れ出る情熱のままさあ歩き出そう
To save my dream
You need to control your room, Noelle
I'm trying to
Help me
What's your hand treatment, mister?
Keep your paws up my wheel, it's one day
Guys, trees
Stop shaking the broom, Osta
I'll lose control of it
OK, but I'm pretty sure you weren't in control to begin with
That's why I told you I would run instead
But no!
You were like, oh, if you're going to Hodge Village
I mean, I guess I could take you there
If you insist
I've got total control of my broom now
WIRE!
It's not like you could've run that far anyway
How many days would that have taken you?
You can't exactly complain
When I was nice enough to give you a free ride
If it cost me my life, then it's not free!
I'm going ahead, see you there
Hey, that's no fair, Nero
Take me with you!
Wait!
Nero!
There, you see?
What did I tell you before?
I'm completely in control of my magic
Which means everything is okay
So you've got absolutely nothing to worry about
Oh man
Why didn't I just let Finral make a portal for me?
Whoa!
Looks like we're almost there
I can see the demon head
Oh, yeah
Show some gratitude
I'm royalty, you know
You know
Hey, don't just
There's the meathead
Yup, he gives new meaning to the word
Hey, are you guys on your way to visit Hosh Village too?
Yeah
Captain Vongence gave me permission
Then it's settled
Let's make it a contest!
What kind of contest?
We're in a race to see who gets to the church faster!
And it'll be me for sure!
Seriously? A race?
I mean, come on
You're not a couple of children
Right, you know?
He's such an idiot
We're lucky the damage wasn't significant in this area
Yeah, it could have been a lot worse for sure
What's that?
I don't know
Eat my dust!
I'm almost there!
Took you long enough
Aah!
Looks like I won your contest
Aah, please!
You barely even beat me here!
Yeah, but I still won
Aah!
You know's acting kind of childish too
You're so cute when you're competitive
Aah!
And now you're getting all embarrassed
That makes you even more adorable
Aah!
That's the truth behind it.
I understand.
As a matter of fact, when that article came out, no one around here believed it.
Because they know you.
And they know that you two saved our village.
Trust me, we couldn't be prouder of you.
Really? Thank you.
Do you know what I did with that paper?
I hung it up in a nice frame!
Why, though?
Would you mind signing it, too?
Come on!
Where are the kids?
They're gone!
Did something happen to them? Where'd they go?
Oh, Ashton, you know.
Those dear children.
Every last one of them has left!
A school?
That's right!
We finally got the magic school that all the kids wanted.
At last, we managed to open it.
What a blessing!
Especially considering the many hardships we've suffered because the capital ignores our poor village.
We were so inspired when you joined the magic knights.
And with a bit of hard work, we accomplished something wonderful!
Sister Lily's an instructor there, so she's keeping fairly busy.
Wow! Those kids are lucky!
I teach a few lessons every now and then myself!
Hey! Welcome back, guys!
Asta!
Yuno! Thanks for saving the village!
Sure!
That's the school building there.
The whole village worked together to repurpose our old pop-potato storage.
We used to play hide-and-seek in there all the time, do you remember?
I don't think we did.
Of course we did!
You'd hide in there until it got dark, and then you would start crying because I couldn't find you.
How could you forget that?
Never happened.
Oh, deny it all you want.
We both know it's true.
My prince...
Hey! You guys, look who's here!
Yay! Welcome home!
Home!
Thanks! We're really glad to be back!
Is that them?
Oh, easy!
Yay!
They really came home!
We missed you!
Asta, have you grown up at all?
You're still short.
I have!
But obviously you're as cool as always, Yuno.
Actually, Yuno's more than just cool.
He's also extremely cute.
Wow!
It's some kind of talking doll!
She's not a doll.
She's the wind spirit.
Spirit!
It's Belle.
I'd prefer if you didn't treat me like a toy this time.
Hey, Brad is a pretty doll to play with.
Yay!
She's so neat!
Let me hold her!
I'm gonna have someone to just say, Yuno, help!
Asta, you know.
You're both safe.
Oh, that makes me so happy.
Sister Lily.
Will you please marry me?
Of course.
Some things never change.
Yeah, back when Asta lived in the village, we'd hear marriage proposals every day.
I think I finally got the hang of this thing.
Will you please marry me?
No!
I'm just proposing!
Come on, you can't just spring that on me out of nowhere!
Yep, just like I remember.
Old habit.
Sorry.
You clumsy moron!
How dare you get in the way of my perfect broom landing!
As for your proposal...
Um, well, I'm not sure how to respond to that.
It's so sudden.
Huh?
Hello, young lady.
Judging by that robe, I assume you're one of Asta's cohorts from the Black Bulls.
Yes, sir.
We appreciate you keeping an eye on Asta here.
You must be Noel.
He sends us letters about his adventures and your name comes up pretty often.
Letters?
Is that true?
This is a surprise.
What could he possibly be telling them about me?
Maybe it's like...
I've got my heart set on a very special lady.
Her name's...
Noel.
Don't say that stuff!
What are they yelling about now?
Excuse me, miss.
Are you also with the Black Bulls?
Oh, yeah.
That's Nero, our newest squad member.
Nice to meet you.
We hope you'll continue to look after Asta for us.
I'll do my best.
By the way, I understand you just got here, but I do have a small favor to ask of you boys if it isn't too much.
Of course.
Anything!
Whatever you want, I'll make it happen!
Well, it would really mean a lot to me if you could come and work as teachers at the magic school for the day.
Me and Yuno, as teachers?
Mm-hmm.
They look up to you, like everyone else in the Clover Kingdom does.
So I think it would be a lovely memory for them to receive a lesson from some real magic knights.
They've grown up so much, it warms my heart.
Teacher Asuka!
Teacher Yuno!
Teacher!
All right, watch and learn.
I'm going to teach you kids everything you need to know to be awesome magic knights.
Listen one!
Magic equals muscles!
I'm afraid I don't follow you.
Since you guys are little, you don't have much mana yet.
But there's one way you can make up for it.
That's right, with muscles!
So you gotta train really hard!
Starting right now!
Let's run laps!
Interesting teaching style.
Teacher Yuno!
While Asta's busy with that, would you mind being the girls' instructor, please?
I'm not sure.
It's all right, you don't need to place too much importance on teaching them specific things.
Just playing with them for a while is good enough.
So I'm babysitting.
Yes, I'm sure the children will learn a thing or two simply by observing you.
Yeah, I guess.
Teacher Yuno!
I want to play house!
That sounds great.
Why do I have to be the baby?
I mean, I'm royalty!
Ah, Noel!
You're a cute baby!
Yeah, you think so?
If I'm doing it, I might as well do it right.
Okay, I'm a baby.
Here goes!
Wee!
See?
You can do it!
Mama, get her to stop crying!
Okay.
Um, there, there.
That's not how you be a mom!
You're supposed to be nicer to your kid!
Be nicer?
Sister.
Remember what I said?
Dad, the children learn by watching you, so you need to take this seriously.
Right, I'll do that.
Now, now, little one.
Mommy's here.
There's no need to cry.
Ah, you must be hungry, right?
Let me give you some milk.
There you go.
Oh, is it good?
Go on, drink some more.
Oh, goodness, Parham.
You've got some ketchup on your face.
Oh, you little rascal.
What am I going to do with you?
I wonder who you take after.
Must be that Papa.
Look at him playing house.
What a sweet boy.
Oh, I can't imagine what those children are going to take away from this.
This is the New Leaves class.
They're working hard to prepare for the day when they get their grimoires.
Oh, the awarding ceremony.
Feels like forever since we had ours.
But I guess it wasn't really that long ago.
Not at all.
That's it.
Good job, guys.
I know them.
Yeah.
That's enough.
Wonderful job.
I'm so proud of you.
Looks like all that studying is starting to pay off.
Keep it up.
Yes, sir.
Well, if it isn't you know an Asta.
It's really great to see you again.
You guys, we missed you.
You know.
Sorry for how we acted back then.
The truth is, when we saw how great you became,
we decided to turn over a new leaf and work as assistant teachers here.
They're good guys now?
Did you hit your heads or something?
Oh, headmaster.
Who's the headmaster?
Hey, that's the old guy who gives out the grimoires.
Hello, boys.
Good to see you back in the village.
I've heard about all your astounding accomplishments.
You've made us quite proud.
The great things you've done have motivated the children to work hard in their study of magic.
That's why this school was opened.
We've really made a difference, huh?
Now, then, the grimoire tower is home to a multitude of powerful grimoires,
each one waiting to be awarded to its future master.
However, no two tomes are alike.
They vary in size and thickness.
But you children will be the ones to increase the number and potency of the spells within them.
With a bit of hard work, you can be anything you wish.
You can even emulate these courageous heroes.
My dream for this village is that some of you boys and girls will follow the new nose in Asta's footsteps
and go up to become brave magic knights like they are.
So don't let me down!
Okay!
I see.
So you'll be leaving us first thing in the morning, then.
We'll be throwing a big party tonight with all the pot potatoes you can eat!
I know you boys are excited about that.
Yeah.
Miss Noel, I hope you and Miss Nero will be able to join us for the festivities.
Sure, thanks a lot.
I know it'll dry my mouth out again, though.
Huh?
That looks like Nash.
Hey!
Wait up!
Oh, it's just Asta.
Ah, don't give me that.
Anyway, how come I didn't see you at the magic school earlier?
Did you skip?
There was something I needed to do.
Oh, yeah?
And what was that?
Mind your own business, alright?
Hey, don't just run away from me!
Come back!
You shouldn't be playing hooky!
Don't worry.
There haven't been any issues with Nash's attendance at all.
Right.
We're pretending we don't know what he's been up to.
I'm sure you remember how much he admires Asta.
After you two left home, he said he wanted to be like him and join the magic knights one day.
Well, that makes sense.
Two hundred ninety-eight, two hundred ninety-nine, three hundred!
Gotta chuck some Moguro juice and build up my magic power!
More!
So gross!
A little more!
Alright!
My mana's overflowing now!
Even though I'm poor and an orphan, I'll prove that I can be more amazing than anyone else in the world!
Just like Asta.
My prince, please keep watching over them
This kingdom has a bright future
I can tell
I thought I'd bring over some pot potatoes
Those boys must be starving from their trip
Thank you
Do you need some help, father?
I can feel that for you if you like
You're too kind
Good grief
Where did Asta run off to?
Scratch that
What I really want to know is what he wrote about me in all those letters home
Come here to cry?
Hey, you can see I'm not crying
I'm just happy
We were both orphans
But unlike you, I was the kid who had no magic power
I got made fun of all the time
Then
Hello, boys
Good to see you back in the village
I've heard about all your astounding accomplishments
You've made us quite proud
That felt good
Of course it did
Because we really have accomplished a lot of great things
We've proven that with hard work
You can become anything you want
But still, our story's not over yet
It's only the beginning, Asta
Yeah
If we're about to go up against the Spade Kingdom
And the Devils
The only way we'll succeed is by making ourselves even stronger
Let's protect everyone
And keep moving forward
You think we're ready for this, you know?
I know I am
I'm gonna be better than you can even comprehend
Well, for now I'd say we're about equal
Sure, whatever
I'm gonna be better
Friendship
What if we live here
It's hard on
Eles
We're about to study
selbst
And
We're about to walk
obvious
We try
We're not
過ご
It'sver Putting
worthy
I never
We don't many
I need to be afraid of the truth
I'm not sure if I'm wrong
You're not alone
You're only one person
I'm not alone
I'm the next wizard king
No matter what obstacles stand in my way
I'll overcome them all
I'll grow stronger
Black Clover, page 132
The Lion Awakens
I'm not the only one trying to improve
The Lifestyle
The Lion Awakens
Bremen
From the Middle East
The Lion Awakens
The Lion Your iconic
The Lion begins
The Lion Awakens
And wasidir